const periodicTable = [
  {
    atomicNumber: 1,
    nameFront: "Hydrogen",
    nameBack: "HTML",
    symbolFront: "H",
    symbolBack: "H",
    position: { row: 1, column: 1 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 2 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 3 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 4 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 5 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 6 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 7 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 8 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 9 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 10 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 11 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 12 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 13 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 14 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 15 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 16 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 1, column: 17 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 2,
    nameFront: "Helium",
    nameBack: "CSS",
    symbolFront: "He",
    symbolBack: "Cs",
    position: { row: 1, column: 18 },
    classification: "noble-gas",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 3,
    nameFront: "Lithium",
    nameBack: "Node",
    symbolFront: "Li",
    symbolBack: "N",
    position: { row: 2, column: 1 },
    classification: "alkali-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 4,
    nameFront: "Beryllium",
    nameBack: "Python",
    symbolFront: "Be",
    symbolBack: "P",
    position: { row: 2, column: 2 },
    classification: "alkaline",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 3 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 4 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 5 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 6 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 7 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 8 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 9 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 10 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 2, column: 11 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 5,
    nameFront: "Boron",
    nameBack: "Java",
    symbolFront: "B",
    symbolBack: "J",
    position: { row: 2, column: 13 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 6,
    nameFront: "Carbon",
    nameBack: "C++",
    symbolFront: "C",
    symbolBack: "C",
    position: { row: 2, column: 14 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 7,
    nameFront: "Nitrogen",
    nameBack: "C Sharp",
    symbolFront: "N",
    symbolBack: "C#",
    position: { row: 2, column: 15 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 8,
    nameFront: "Oxygen",
    nameBack: "Swift",
    symbolFront: "O",
    symbolBack: "S",
    position: { row: 2, column: 16 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 9,
    nameFront: "Fluorine",
    nameBack: "Ruby",
    symbolFront: "F",
    symbolBack: "R",
    position: { row: 2, column: 17 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 10,
    nameFront: "Neon",
    nameBack: "Go",
    symbolFront: "Ne",
    symbolBack: "G",
    position: { row: 2, column: 18 },
    classification: "noble-gas",
  },

  {
    atomicNumber: 11,
    nameFront: "Sodium",
    nameBack: "Rust",
    symbolFront: "Na",
    symbolBack: "Ru",
    position: { row: 3, column: 1 },
    classification: "alkali-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 12,
    nameFront: "Magnesium",
    nameBack: "Typescript",
    symbolFront: "Mg",
    symbolBack: "T",
    position: { row: 3, column: 2 },
    classification: "alkaline",
  },

  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 3 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 4 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 5 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 6 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 7 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 8 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 9 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 10 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 11 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 3, column: 12 },
    isGap: true,
  },

  {
    atomicNumber: 13,
    nameFront: "Aluminum",
    nameBack: "SQL",
    symbolFront: "Al",
    symbolBack: "S",
    position: { row: 3, column: 13 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 14,
    nameFront: "Silicon",
    nameBack: "PHP",
    symbolFront: "Si",
    symbolBack: "P",
    position: { row: 3, column: 14 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 15,
    nameFront: "Phosphorus",
    nameBack: "Kotlin",
    symbolFront: "P",
    symbolBack: "K",
    position: { row: 3, column: 15 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 16,
    nameFront: "Sulfur",
    nameBack: "React",
    symbolFront: "S",
    symbolBack: "Re",
    position: { row: 3, column: 16 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 17,
    nameFront: "Chlorine",
    nameBack: "Vue",
    symbolFront: "Cl",
    symbolBack: "V",
    position: { row: 3, column: 17 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 18,
    nameFront: "Argon",
    nameBack: "Express",
    symbolFront: "Ar",
    symbolBack: "E",
    position: { row: 3, column: 18 },
    classification: "noble-gas",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 19,
    nameFront: "Potassium",
    nameBack: "Twilio",
    symbolFront: "K",
    symbolBack: "T",
    position: { row: 4, column: 1 },
    classification: "alkali-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 20,
    nameFront: "Calcium",
    nameBack: "Next",
    symbolFront: "Ca",
    symbolBack: "N",
    position: { row: 4, column: 2 },
    classification: "alkaline",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 21,
    nameFront: "Scandium",
    nameBack: "Angular",
    symbolFront: "Sc",
    symbolBack: "A",
    position: { row: 4, column: 3 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 22,
    nameFront: "Titanium",
    nameBack: "Svelte",
    symbolFront: "Ti",
    symbolBack: "Sv",
    position: { row: 4, column: 4 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 23,
    nameFront: "Vanadium",
    nameBack: "React Native",
    symbolFront: "V",
    symbolBack: "Rn",
    position: { row: 4, column: 5 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 24,
    nameFront: "Chromium",
    nameBack: "Mapbox Gl",
    symbolFront: "Cr",
    symbolBack: "Mg",
    position: { row: 4, column: 6 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 25,
    nameFront: "Manganese",
    nameBack: "Electron",
    symbolFront: "Mn",
    symbolBack: "E",
    position: { row: 4, column: 7 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 26,
    nameFront: "Iron",
    nameBack: "Redux",
    symbolFront: "Fe",
    symbolBack: "Rx",
    position: { row: 4, column: 8 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 27,
    nameFront: "Cobalt",
    nameBack: "Azure",
    symbolFront: "Co",
    symbolBack: "Az",
    position: { row: 4, column: 9 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 28,
    nameFront: "Nickel",
    nameBack: "AWS",
    symbolFront: "Ni",
    symbolBack: "A",
    position: { row: 4, column: 10 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 29,
    nameFront: "Copper",
    nameBack: "GCP",
    symbolFront: "Cu",
    symbolBack: "G",
    position: { row: 4, column: 11 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 30,
    nameFront: "Zinc",
    nameBack: "Salesforce",
    symbolFront: "Zn",
    symbolBack: "Sf",
    position: { row: 4, column: 12 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 31,
    nameFront: "Gallium",
    nameBack: "Firebase",
    symbolFront: "Ga",
    symbolBack: "Fi",
    position: { row: 4, column: 13 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 32,
    nameFront: "Germanium",
    nameBack: "Tailwind",
    symbolFront: "Ge",
    symbolBack: "T",
    position: { row: 4, column: 14 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 33,
    nameFront: "Arsenic",
    nameBack: "Django",
    symbolFront: "As",
    symbolBack: "Dj",
    position: { row: 4, column: 15 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 34,
    nameFront: "Selenium",
    nameBack: "Nuxt",
    symbolFront: "Se",
    symbolBack: "Nu",
    position: { row: 4, column: 16 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 35,
    nameFront: "Bromine",
    nameBack: "Bootstrap",
    symbolFront: "Br",
    symbolBack: "B",
    position: { row: 4, column: 17 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 36,
    nameFront: "Krypton",
    nameBack: "Bash",
    symbolFront: "Kr",
    symbolBack: "Ba",
    position: { row: 4, column: 18 },
    classification: "noble-gas",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 37,
    nameFront: "Rubidium",
    nameBack: "Clojure",
    symbolFront: "Rb",
    symbolBack: "Cl",
    position: { row: 5, column: 1 },
    classification: "alkali-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 38,
    nameFront: "Strontium",
    nameBack: "CoffeeScript",
    symbolFront: "Sr",
    symbolBack: "Cs",
    position: { row: 5, column: 2 },
    classification: "alkaline",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 39,
    nameFront: "Yttrium",
    nameBack: "PureScript",
    symbolFront: "Y",
    symbolBack: "Ps",
    position: { row: 5, column: 3 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 40,
    nameFront: "Zirconium",
    nameBack: "AppleScript",
    symbolFront: "Zr",
    symbolBack: "As",
    position: { row: 5, column: 4 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 41,
    nameFront: "Niobium",
    nameBack: "ECMAScript",
    symbolFront: "Nb",
    symbolBack: "Es",
    position: { row: 5, column: 5 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 42,
    nameFront: "Molybdenum",
    nameBack: "Google Apss Scripp",
    symbolFront: "Mo",
    symbolBack: "Gs",
    position: { row: 5, column: 6 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 43,
    nameFront: "Technetium",
    nameBack: "JScript",
    symbolFront: "Tc",
    symbolBack: "J",
    position: { row: 5, column: 7 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 44,
    nameFront: "Ruthenium",
    nameBack: "Lotus Script",
    symbolFront: "Ru",
    symbolBack: "Ls",
    position: { row: 5, column: 8 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 45,
    nameFront: "Rhodium",
    nameBack: "PostScript",
    symbolFront: "Rh",
    symbolBack: "Pt",
    position: { row: 5, column: 9 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 46,
    nameFront: "Palladium",
    nameBack: "Scala",
    symbolFront: "Pd",
    symbolBack: "Sc",
    position: { row: 5, column: 10 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 47,
    nameFront: "Silver",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "Ag",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 5, column: 11 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 48,
    nameFront: "Cadmium",
    nameBack: "Vim",
    symbolFront: "Cd",
    symbolBack: "V",
    position: { row: 5, column: 12 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 49,
    nameFront: "Indium",
    nameBack: "Dart",
    symbolFront: "In",
    symbolBack: "D",
    position: { row: 5, column: 13 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 50,
    nameFront: "Tin",
    nameBack: "Serverless",
    symbolFront: "Sn",
    symbolBack: "Sl",
    position: { row: 5, column: 14 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 51,
    nameFront: "Antimony",
    nameBack: "Graph QL",
    symbolFront: "Sb",
    symbolBack: "G",
    position: { row: 5, column: 15 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 52,
    nameFront: "Tellurium",
    nameBack: "Markup Down",
    symbolFront: "Te",
    symbolBack: "Md",
    position: { row: 5, column: 16 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 53,
    nameFront: "Iodine",
    nameBack: "Clipper",
    symbolFront: "I",
    symbolBack: "Cl",
    position: { row: 5, column: 17 },
    classification: "diatomic-nonmetal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 54,
    nameFront: "Xenon",
    nameBack: "Pascal",
    symbolFront: "Xe",
    symbolBack: "Pa",
    position: { row: 5, column: 18 },
    classification: "noble-gas",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 55,
    nameFront: "Cesium",
    nameBack: "Pure",
    symbolFront: "Cs",
    symbolBack: "Pu",
    position: { row: 6, column: 1 },
    classification: "alkali-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 56,
    nameFront: "Barium",
    nameBack: "Red",
    symbolFront: "Ba",
    symbolBack: "R",
    position: { row: 6, column: 2 },
    classification: "alkaline",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 6, column: 3 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 72,
    nameFront: "Hafnium",
    nameBack: "ECLiPSe",
    symbolFront: "Hf",
    symbolBack: "E",
    position: { row: 6, column: 4 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 73,
    nameFront: "Tantalum",
    nameBack: "Whiley",
    symbolFront: "Ta",
    symbolBack: "W",
    position: { row: 6, column: 5 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 74,
    nameFront: "Tungsten",
    nameBack: "Joy",
    symbolFront: "W",
    symbolBack: "Jy",
    position: { row: 6, column: 6 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 75,
    nameFront: "Rhenium",
    nameBack: "JMP",
    symbolFront: "Re",
    symbolBack: "Jp",
    position: { row: 6, column: 7 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 76,
    nameFront: "Osmium",
    nameBack: "Ceylon",
    symbolFront: "Os",
    symbolBack: "Ce",
    position: { row: 6, column: 8 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 77,
    nameFront: "Iridium",
    nameBack: "Mojo",
    symbolFront: "Ir",
    symbolBack: "M",
    position: { row: 6, column: 9 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 78,
    nameFront: "Platinum",
    nameBack: "Ember",
    symbolFront: "Pt",
    symbolBack: "Em",
    position: { row: 6, column: 10 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 79,
    nameFront: "Gold",
    nameBack: "Jquery",
    symbolFront: "Au",
    symbolBack: "Jq",
    position: { row: 6, column: 11 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 80,
    nameFront: "Mercury",
    nameBack: "Backbone",
    symbolFront: "Hg",
    symbolBack: "Bb",
    position: { row: 6, column: 12 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 81,
    nameFront: "Thallium",
    nameBack: "Websockets",
    symbolFront: "Tl",
    symbolBack: "Ws",
    position: { row: 6, column: 13 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 82,
    nameFront: "Lead",
    nameBack: "JSON",
    symbolFront: "Pb",
    symbolBack: "J",
    position: { row: 6, column: 14 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 83,
    nameFront: "Bismuth",
    nameBack: "Semantic UI",
    symbolFront: "Bi",
    symbolBack: "Su",
    position: { row: 6, column: 15 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 84,
    nameFront: "Polonium",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "Po",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 6, column: 16 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 85,
    nameFront: "Astatine",
    nameBack: "Foundation",
    symbolFront: "At",
    symbolBack: "F",
    position: { row: 6, column: 17 },
    classification: "metalloid",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 86,
    nameFront: "Radon",
    nameBack: "Meteor",
    symbolFront: "Rn",
    symbolBack: "Me",
    position: { row: 6, column: 18 },
    classification: "noble-gas",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 87,
    nameFront: "Francium",
    nameBack: "Mithril",
    symbolFront: "Fr",
    symbolBack: "Mi",
    position: { row: 7, column: 1 },
    classification: "alkali-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 88,
    nameFront: "Radium",
    nameBack: "Alpine",
    symbolFront: "Ra",
    symbolBack: "A",
    position: { row: 7, column: 2 },
    classification: "alkaline",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: null,
    nameFront: "",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 7, column: 3 },
    isGap: true,
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 104,
    nameFront: "Rutherfordium",
    nameBack: "Preact",
    symbolFront: "Rf",
    symbolBack: "Pr",
    position: { row: 7, column: 4 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 105,
    nameFront: "Dubnium",
    nameBack: "Gatsby",
    symbolFront: "Db",
    symbolBack: "G",
    position: { row: 7, column: 5 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 106,
    nameFront: "Seaborgium",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "Sg",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 7, column: 6 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 107,
    nameFront: "Bohrium",
    nameBack: "Jest",
    symbolFront: "Bh",
    symbolBack: "Je",
    position: { row: 7, column: 7 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 108,
    nameFront: "Hassium",
    nameBack: "Enzyme",
    symbolFront: "Hs",
    symbolBack: "Ez",
    position: { row: 7, column: 8 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 109,
    nameFront: "Meitnerium",
    nameBack: "Chai",
    symbolFront: "Mt",
    symbolBack: "Ch",
    position: { row: 7, column: 9 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 110,
    nameFront: "Darmstadtium",
    nameBack: "Jasmine",
    symbolFront: "Ds",
    symbolBack: "Ja",
    position: { row: 7, column: 10 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 111,
    nameFront: "Roentgenium",
    nameBack: "Mocha",
    symbolFront: "Rg",
    symbolBack: "Mo",
    position: { row: 7, column: 11 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 112,
    nameFront: "Copernicium",
    nameBack: "Spring Boot",
    symbolFront: "Cn",
    symbolBack: "Sb",
    position: { row: 7, column: 12 },
    classification: "transition-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 113,
    nameFront: "Nihonium",
    nameBack: "Sails",
    symbolFront: "Nh",
    symbolBack: "Sa",
    position: { row: 7, column: 13 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 114,
    nameFront: "Flerovium",
    nameBack: "Objective C",
    symbolFront: "Fl",
    symbolBack: "O",
    position: { row: 7, column: 14 },
    classification: "post-transition-metals",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 115,
    nameFront: "Moscovium",
    nameBack: "Material UI",
    symbolFront: "Mc",
    symbolBack: "Mu",
    position: { row: 7, column: 15 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 116,
    nameFront: "Livermorium",
    nameBack: "Prisma",
    symbolFront: "Lv",
    symbolBack: "P",
    position: { row: 7, column: 16 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 117,
    nameFront: "Tennessine",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "Ts",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 7, column: 17 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 118,
    nameFront: "Oganesson",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "Og",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 7, column: 18 },
    classification: "unknown",
  },

  {
    atomicNumber: 57,
    nameFront: "Lanthanum",
    nameBack: ".NET",
    symbolFront: "La",
    symbolBack: "Ne",
    position: { row: 6, column: 3 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 58,
    nameFront: "Cerium",
    nameBack: "MonogDB",
    symbolFront: "Ce",
    symbolBack: "Mn",
    position: { row: 8, column: 4 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 59,
    nameFront: "Praseodymium",
    nameBack: "MySQL",
    symbolFront: "Pr",
    symbolBack: "My",
    position: { row: 8, column: 5 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 60,
    nameFront: "Neodymium",
    nameBack: "Docker",
    symbolFront: "Nd",
    symbolBack: "D",
    position: { row: 8, column: 6 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 61,
    nameFront: "Promethium",
    nameBack: "Kubernetes",
    symbolFront: "Pm",
    symbolBack: "Ku",
    position: { row: 8, column: 7 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 62,
    nameFront: "Samarium",
    nameBack: "Sass",
    symbolFront: "Sm",
    symbolBack: "Sa",
    position: { row: 8, column: 8 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 63,
    nameFront: "Europium",
    nameBack: "Webpack",
    symbolFront: "Eu",
    symbolBack: "W",
    position: { row: 8, column: 9 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 64,
    nameFront: "Gadolinium",
    nameBack: "Maven",
    symbolFront: "Gd",
    symbolBack: "Mv",
    position: { row: 8, column: 10 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 65,
    nameFront: "Terbium",
    nameBack: "Flask",
    symbolFront: "Tb",
    symbolBack: "Fl",
    position: { row: 8, column: 11 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 66,
    nameFront: "Dysprosium",
    nameBack: "Haskel",
    symbolFront: "Dy",
    symbolBack: "H",
    position: { row: 8, column: 12 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 67,
    nameFront: "Holmium",
    nameBack: "",
    symbolFront: "Ho",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 8, column: 13 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 68,
    nameFront: "Erbium",
    nameBack: "Stimulus",
    symbolFront: "Er",
    symbolBack: "",
    position: { row: 8, column: 14 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 69,
    nameFront: "Thulium",
    nameBack: "Three",
    symbolFront: "Tm",
    symbolBack: "Th",
    position: { row: 8, column: 15 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 70,
    nameFront: "Ytterbium",
    nameBack: "D3",
    symbolFront: "Yb",
    symbolBack: "D3",
    position: { row: 8, column: 16 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 71,
    nameFront: "Lutetium",
    nameBack: "Chart",
    symbolFront: "Lu",
    symbolBack: "Ch",
    position: { row: 8, column: 17 },
    classification: "polyatomic-non-metal",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 89,
    nameFront: "Actinium",
    nameBack: "Falcon",
    symbolFront: "Ac",
    symbolBack: "Fa",
    position: { row: 7, column: 3 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 90,
    nameFront: "Thorium",
    nameBack: "Paper",
    symbolFront: "Th",
    symbolBack: "Pa",
    position: { row: 9, column: 4 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 91,
    nameFront: "Protactinium",
    nameBack: "Babylon",
    symbolFront: "Pa",
    symbolBack: "B",
    position: { row: 9, column: 5 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 92,
    nameFront: "Uranium",
    nameBack: "Ploty",
    symbolFront: "U",
    symbolBack: "Pl",
    position: { row: 9, column: 6 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 93,
    nameFront: "Neptunium",
    nameBack: "Pixi",
    symbolFront: "Np",
    symbolBack: "Pi",
    position: { row: 9, column: 7 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 94,
    nameFront: "Plutonium",
    nameBack: "Socket IO",
    symbolFront: "Pu",
    symbolBack: "So",
    position: { row: 9, column: 8 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 95,
    nameFront: "Americium",
    nameBack: "Groovy",
    symbolFront: "Am",
    symbolBack: "Gy",
    position: { row: 9, column: 9 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 96,
    nameFront: "Curium",
    nameBack: "Nim",
    symbolFront: "Cm",
    symbolBack: "Ni",
    position: { row: 9, column: 10 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 97,
    nameFront: "Berkelium",
    nameBack: "Quasar",
    symbolFront: "Bk",
    symbolBack: "Q",
    position: { row: 9, column: 11 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 98,
    nameFront: "Californium",
    nameBack: "Bulma",
    symbolFront: "Cf",
    symbolBack: "Bu",
    position: { row: 9, column: 12 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 99,
    nameFront: "Einsteinium",
    nameBack: "Laravel",
    symbolFront: "Es",
    symbolBack: "La",
    position: { row: 9, column: 13 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 100,
    nameFront: "Fermium",
    nameBack: "Knockout",
    symbolFront: "Fm",
    symbolBack: "Ko",
    position: { row: 9, column: 14 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 101,
    nameFront: "Mendelevium",
    nameBack: "MobX",
    symbolFront: "Md",
    symbolBack: "Mx",
    position: { row: 9, column: 15 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 102,
    nameFront: "Nobelium",
    nameBack: "Grindsome",
    symbolFront: "No",
    symbolBack: "Gr",
    position: { row: 9, column: 16 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
  {
    atomicNumber: 103,
    nameFront: "Lawrencium",
    nameBack: "Alpine",
    symbolFront: "Lr",
    symbolBack: "Al",
    position: { row: 9, column: 17 },
    classification: "actinide",
  },
];

export default periodicTable;
